Lynn Hershman-Leeson Papers M1452
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Audio-Visual Materials, 1
  - Subseries 1.40: Shadow's Song, 1.40
    - Reel 1; 1990-10-16 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 16mm; Negative (Carton 27, Folder 6)
    - Reel 2; 1990-10-16 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 16mm; Negative (Carton 27, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 1.41: Shooting Script, 1.41
    - [unidentified]; undated, [unidentified director/producer] (1 items), Film: 16mm Full Coat Magnetic; Soundtrack (Carton 27, Folder 8)
    - [sound color movie film], (1 item), Film: Super 8; Cartrdige (Carton 27, Folder 9)
    - [Slam #1-3]; undated (3 items), Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 40, Folder 1)
    - Bram Dress; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 40, Folder 2)
    - Double [illegible]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 40, Folder 3)
    - Voice Over 1st [illegible]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 40, Folder 4)
    - PAL [illegible] Dub; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 40, Folder 5)
    - Danish, Window; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 40, Folder 6)
    - [illegible]; -06-10 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 40, Folder 7)
    - Jaalom; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 40, Folder 8)
    - [Shooting Script various footage]; undated (6 items), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min., 60 min. (Carton 40, Folder 9)
    - [illegible] Finished; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min.; 00:56:00:00 (Carton 40, Folder 10)
    - New Window, Christine [illegible]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min.; 00:13:00:00 (Carton 40, Folder 11)
    - [Danish footage]; undated (3 items), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 40, Folder 12)
    - [illegible]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element] (Carton 40, Folder 13)
    - [Shooting Script various footage]; undated (2 items), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 41, Folder 1)
    - Christine; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 41, Folder 2)
    - Scenes from the Danes, Seg. 9-16 + raw material; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 41, Folder 3)
    - Final; 1992 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 75 min.; 00:66:00:00 (Carton 41, Folder 4)
    - 3/4 [illegible] PAL; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min.; 00:13:00:00 (Carton 41, Folder 5)
    - [illegible] sound; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 41, Folder 6)
    - Christine Day2, Blond wig; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 41, Folder 7)
    - Letter 5; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 41, Folder 8)
    - ANA Medieta Window Dubs; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 41, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 1.42: Teknolust, 1.42
    - Teknolust Version CC; 2001-06-20 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Master; 90 min. (Carton 25, Folder 1)
    - Teknolust cut; 2001-05-02 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 90 min. (Carton 25, Folder 2)
    - newest transfer; 2000-09-19 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 46, Folder 1)
    - [Teknolust Roll #1A, 1B, 8,9, 10B, 11, 13, 16, 17B, 18B, 19A, 19B, 21, 23, 26, 30, 34, 35, 39-40, 43, 45A, 45B, 48, 50A, 50B, 51, 52B, 53; 2000-12 (29 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 46, Folder 2)
    - [Teknolust Roll #47, 52B]; 2000-12-20 (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: HDCAM; Dub; 40 min., 22 min.; 00:30:03:00; 00:06:15:00 (Carton 46, Folder 3)
    - [Tape Reel 2, 4-6, 15, 20, 22, 27-29, 31]; 2000 (11 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 47, Folder 1)
    - Made for Each Other; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 60 min.; 01:32:00:00 (Carton 47, Folder 2)
    - Last Time I Saw Paris Reel 2 of 2; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 60 min.; 00:56:00:00 (Carton 47, Folder 3)
    - The Man with the Golden Arm Part 2 of 2; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 60 min.; 00:60:00:00 (Carton 47, Folder 4)
    - Teknolust with Burn #2; 2001-08-01 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 47, Folder 5)
    - HD Teknolust Roll# 1,7-10, 12, 16-19, 21, 23-25, 30, 33-37, 40, 42 44A, 44B, 45A, 48-49, 51, 52A; 2000-12 (35 items), Video: HDCAM; Dub; 22 min., 40 min. (Carton 53, Folder 1)
    - Technolust Production Sound Master; 2000-11-09 (1 item), Audio: DAT; Master (Carton 54, Folder 2)
    - HD Teknolust Roll# 11, 13, 26, 39, 46, 50A, 53-54; 2000-12 (8 items), Video: HDCAM; Dub; 22 min., 40 min. (Carton 54, Folder 3)
    - Teknolust Test Reel 1A-4A; 2000-11-09 (4 items), Video: HDCAM; Dub; 40 min. (Carton 54, Folder 4)
    - Teknolust Roll# 10, 12(part1), 12(part2), 17-18, 24, 44A, 44B, 46; 2000-12 (9 items), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 54, Folder 5)
    - Teknolust - Roll #37; 2000-12-16 (1 item), Video: Digital Betacam; Dub; 32 min.; 00:27:07:00 (Carton 54, Folder 6)
    - Teknolust Roll 19/New Donut Shop; 2000-12-05 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min.; 00:28:19:00 (Carton 54, Folder 7)
    - Reel #14; 2000-12-21 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min.; 00:30:00:00 (Carton 54, Folder 8)
    - Reel #6B; 2000-12-21 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min.; 00:30:00:00 (Carton 54, Folder 9)
    - DV1, DV2; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 54, Folder 10)
    - Roll# 1, 18, 41; 2000 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 54, Folder 11)
    - [unidentified]; 2000-11-22 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: DVCAM; Dub; 40 min. (Carton 54, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 1.43: Teleprescence, 1.43
    - Dub; 1992-03-29 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min.; 00:03:00:00 (Carton 17, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 1.44: Test Patterns, 1.44
    - [VHS Dub]; 1979 (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: VHS; Dub; 00:14:00:00 (Carton 36, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 1.45: Twists in the Cord, 1.45
    - Twisted Cord #10, 20, 21, 23; undated (2 items), Audio: Cassette; Dub; 90 min. (Carton 25, Folder 3)
    - Twisted Cord; 1994 (9 items), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min. (Carton 25, Folder 4)
    - Music Work Tape; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 25, Folder 5)
    - Twisted Cord #14; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 25, Folder 6)
    - [VHS Dub]; 1994 (3 items), Video: VHS; Dub; 00:55:00:00 (Carton 25, Folder 7)
    - [various footage]; undated (2 items), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 25, Folder 8)
    - [various footage]; undated (6 items), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min. (Carton 25, Folder 9)
    - Telephone Archive; 1994-08 (1 item), Video: Hi8; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 25, Folder 10)
    - Dislocation Test; -08-26 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Hi8; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 25, Folder 11)
    - Dub; 1994-09-19 (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 25, Folder 12)
    - Twisted Cord #23 Work Tape Music; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 25, Folder 13)
    - [various audio]; undated (3 items), Audio: Cassette; Dub (Carton 45, Folder 3)
    - [I Want You Mix Masters]; undated (1 item), Audio: DAT; Master; 30 min. (Carton 45, Folder 4)
    - Rich Gold; 1994-08-26 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min. (Carton 45, Folder 5)
    - Sandy Stone 1-2; undated (2 items), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 45, Folder 6)
    - Kroeker 1-2; undated (2 items), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 45, Folder 7)
    - R.U.Sirius; 1994-08-12 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 45, Folder 8)
    - Paul Singing; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 45, Folder 9)
    - Minnette Lehmann; 1994-08-12 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 45, Folder 10)
    - Leary 1976; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 45, Folder 11)
    - Margaret Morse; 1994-08-12 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 45, Folder 12)
    - Jaron Linier; 1992-12-15 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 45, Folder 13)
    - Andrew Singer; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min. (Carton 45, Folder 14)
    - [various footage]; undated (12 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 45, Folder 15)
    - [various footage]; undated (10 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min., [1] 60 min. (Carton 45, Folder 16)
    - [various footage/audio]; undated (6 items), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min., 60 min. (Carton 52, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 1.46: Verbatim Transcript of the Last Words of Jim Jones, 1.46
    - Jim Jones Final; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Master; 20 min.; 00:00:07:00 (Carton 36, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 1.47: Virtual Love, 1.47
    - Telepresence, Scott Fisher/R.U. Sirius, Mondo 2000; 1992 (1 item), Audio: Cassette; [unidentified element]; 90 min. (Carton 29, Folder 1)
    - [various audio]; undated (5 items), Audio: Cassette; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 29, Folder 2)
    - Virtual Paradise; undated (1 item), Audio: Cassette; [unidentified element]; 90 min. (Carton 29, Folder 3)
    - Segments + "What's the Catch"; undated (1 item), Audio: DAT; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 29, Folder 4)
    - Audio Dub V.L; undated (2 items), Audio: Cassette; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 29, Folder 5)
    - Sample; undated (2 items), Audio: Cassette; Dub (Carton 29, Folder 6)
    - [music for virtual love]; undated (3 items), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 29, Folder 7)
    - Virtual Love; 1993-06-29 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Master; 20 min. (Carton 29, Folder 8)
    - Val Apt; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min.; 00:16:30:00 (Carton 29, Folder 9)
    - Virtual Love (American Version); 1993-08 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 75 min.; 00:75:00:00 (Carton 29, Folder 10)
    - Trasfer from Hi8, Prerecorded Valerie; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min.; 00:11:00:00 (Carton 29, Folder 11)
    - 2DF Marie w/ glass; 1992-08-10 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 60 min. (Carton 29, Folder 12)
    - Valerie; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 29, Folder 13)
    - 2DF Barry cutaways, Marie at window; 1992-08-10 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 60 min. (Carton 29, Folder 14)
    - 2DF Café,, Childhood photos; 1993-06-03 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min. (Carton 29, Folder 15)
    - 2DF Valerie's Room, Interviews, V.O.'s; 1993-06-03 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min. (Carton 29, Folder 16)
    - Transfer Hi8, 2DF Baby & Twin Babies; 1992-08 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 29, Folder 17)
    - Sue Marcoux Baby Footage, Transferred from VHS; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 29, Folder 18)
    - [Rinde footage]; undated (3 items), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min., 30 min. (Carton 29, Folder 19)
    - [unidentified]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Original; 20 min. (Carton 29, Folder 20)
    - 5th cut, Marie Valerie Art Inst. With interview, 3rd cut Cable scene, Valerie Computer scene; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 29, Folder 21)
    - 1-4 Baby, gunshot, valerie; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 29, Folder 22)
    - [illegible] Fish; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 29, Folder 23)
    - Virtual Love Excerpts; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 00:00:25:00 (Carton 30, Folder 1)
    - [various footage]; undated (5 items), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 30, Folder 2)
    - Twinning Scenes; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 30, Folder 3)
    - Dub; 1993-05-28 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 30, Folder 4)
    - Dub; 1993-06-29 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 5 min.; 00:01:42:00 (Carton 30, Folder 5)
    - Joanne Diary; 1992-08-05 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 30, Folder 6)
    - Exploratorium; 1992-08 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 30, Folder 7)
    - Protection Dub, American Version; 1993-08-17 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 90 min. (Carton 30, Folder 8)
    - Master Edit Protection Dub; 1993-04-19 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 90 min. (Carton 30, Folder 9)
    - Master Edit, 1st cut not Final; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Master; 90 min. (Carton 30, Folder 10)
    - Virutal Love Audio Master; 1993-08-09 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Master; 90 min. (Carton 30, Folder 11)
    - Edited Master; 1993-05-28 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Master (Carton 30, Folder 12)
    - [illegible]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element] (Carton 31, Folder 1)
    - Barry Faked [illegible]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 31, Folder 2)
    - 4th cut; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 31, Folder 3)
    - Rinde; Barry, Robot; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element] (Carton 31, Folder 4)
    - 2nd Cut [various footage]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min.; 00:13:51:00 (Carton 31, Folder 5)
    - [Valerie footage]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 31, Folder 6)
    - 4th edit of cable TV Show, [Jeane footage, Valery footage, Rinde footage, Virtual guides]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 31, Folder 7)
    - [Virtual Love various footage]; undated (7 items), Video: U-matic; Dub (Carton 31, Folder 8)
    - edited documentary + ingrid; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 31, Folder 9)
    - [Various Footage]; undated (4 items), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 31, Folder 10)
    - Young Indy MOW; 1992-01-15 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 31, Folder 11)
    - Virtual Love transfer from 16mm Film; 1992-10-07 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 5 min. (Carton 31, Folder 12)
    - Valery Diary; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 31, Folder 13)
    - [Virtual Love various footage]; undated (15 items), Video: Betacam SP; Master; 30 min. (Carton 32, Folder 1)
    - [Virtual Love various footage]; undated (7 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 32, Folder 2)
    - Virtual Love Scenes Protection dub; 1993-04-19 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 32, Folder 3)
    - [Virtual Love various footage Tape 1,3,4,5]; 1993-06-05 (4 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min. (Carton 32, Folder 4)
    - Wire Frame Graphics; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 33, Folder 1)
    - [various footage]; 1992 (10 items), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 60 min. (Carton 33, Folder 2)
    - [various footage]; 1992 (5 items), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 33, Folder 3)
    - [various footage; undated (5 items), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 33, Folder 4)
    - [Virtual Love Music/Sound Dubs]; undated (3 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min., 20 min. (Carton 51, Folder 1)
    - [I Want You Mix Masters]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master; 30 min. (Carton 51, Folder 2)
    - Lorna; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 30 min.; 00:05:00:00 (Carton 51, Folder 3)
    - Virtual Love Music Cues 1-3; undated (3 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Audio: 1/4" open reel; [unidentified element] (Carton 71, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 1.48: Virtual Voices, 1.48
    - [VHS Dub]; 1994 (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: VHS; Dub; 00:10:00:00 (Carton 36, Folder 18)
  - Subseries 1.49: Lynn Hershman Tribute, 1.49
    - Clip show for Lynn Hershman Tribute; 1994-04-20 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Original; 30 min.; 00:22:00:00 (Carton 43, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 1.50: Lynn Hershman Interviews/Lectures, 1.50
    - [unidentified]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 39, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 1.51: Various Projects by Hershman, 1.51
    - Samples, 1-Proxemics, 2-Endangered species, 3-Lorna Demo; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 21, Folder 1)
    - Prisoner of Paradise and Proxemics; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub (Carton 21, Folder 2)
    - Garden Selects, Disk Demo; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub (Carton 21, Folder 3)
    - Lorna Demonstration, Confessions of a Chameleon, Eyewitness; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub (Carton 21, Folder 4)
    - Confessions of a Chameleon, Eye Witness; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 21, Folder 5)
    - Information White Out, Verbatim Transcription of the ast Tapes of Jim Jones; 1987 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: VHS; Dub; 00:15:00:00 (Carton 21, Folder 6)
    - [Excerpts]; undated (3 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; [1] 20 min., [2] 60 min. (Carton 21, Folder 7)
    - 1.Confessions of a Chameleon, 2. Eye Witness, shortened version; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 21, Folder 8)
    - Double Face, Beautiful People, Found Footage title effects; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 21, Folder 9)
    - Lorna, Deep Contact, [illegible], virtual; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 21, Folder 10)
    - [commercials]; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 21, Folder 11)
    - Demo Tape; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 21, Folder 12)
    - Fish, clouds, wheels, ostriche, snow, flavors; 1985-09-10 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 18 min. (Carton 21, Folder 13)
    - Interactive Installations, Lorna, Deep Contact, Room of One's Own, America's Finest; 1985-09-10 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub (Carton 21, Folder 14)
    - interactive works; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min.; 00:12:00:00 (Carton 21, Folder 15)
    - Lecture Inter(3) Click, Virtual; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: VHS; Dub (Carton 21, Folder 16)
    - Electronic Diary Part 4, Shadow's Song; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: 1" open reel; Master; 7 in. (Carton 69, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 1.52: Unidentified Film, 1.52
    - Godsdog; 1996-06-12 (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub; 15 min. (Carton 8, Folder 5)
    - West Gallery Shots; undated (1 item), Video: 8mm Video; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 8, Folder 6)
    - Communism Dead!; 2000, Ed Jones (1 item), Video: VHS; [unidentified element]; 20 mins.; 00:00:14:00 (Carton 23, Folder 2)
    - Visual Shuffle/Fractured Variations; undated, John Sanborn, Mary Perillo (1 item), Video: VHS; [unidentified element] (Carton 23, Folder 3)
    - [unidentified]; undated (1 item), Video: VHS; [unidentified element] (Carton 33, Folder 5)
    - The Mission; undated, Guillermo, Lorena, & Lynn (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 75 min. (Carton 37, Folder 1)
    - Paull Mancin; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 37, Folder 2)
    - Dance Take, Titles; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 37, Folder 3)
    - [unidentified]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 37, Folder 4)
    - Mat Heckert; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 37, Folder 5)
    - Film; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Sub Master; 20 min. (Carton 37, Folder 6)
    - First 20 min. - Motorcycle, Music Transfer, starts at museum scene; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 37, Folder 7)
    - Lynn 2; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 37, Folder 8)
    - Faceless mixdown; -04-04 (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 30 min.; 00:58:30:00 (Carton 37, Folder 9)
    - D1 Stefano House; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 37, Folder 10)
    - Window dubs, mimi/faith wilding #2, Mimi Shewwpo #10; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 37, Folder 11)
    - [residents music]; undated (3 items), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min., 30 min., 60 min. (Carton 37, Folder 12)
    - Sea; undated (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub; 00:15:00:00 (Carton 37, Folder 13)
    - [unidentified]; undated (1 item), Video: VHS; [unidentified element] (Carton 37, Folder 14)
    - Shooter Seattle All; undated (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub (Carton 37, Folder 15)
    - Marion/Toyogi Dance; undated (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub (Carton 37, Folder 16)
    - Networld + Interop 94, Linda Feferman Shoot Reel #7; 1994-05-04 (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub (Carton 37, Folder 17)
    - Resen Plural; undated (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub; 00:15:00:00 (Carton 37, Folder 18)
    - 1 Sea; undated (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub; 00:15:00:00 (Carton 37, Folder 19)
    - German Sound, Ingred; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 38, Folder 1)
    - BAVC Edit; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 38, Folder 2)
    - [illegible]; undated (2 items), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element] (Carton 38, Folder 3)
    - First Cut, reels 1-3, Commercial test pattern; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min.; 00:27:30:00 (Carton 38, Folder 4)
    - Anne Gerber; 1995-05 (1 item), Video: VHS-C; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 38, Folder 5)
    - Seattle; undated (1 item), Video: Hi-8; [unidentified element] (Carton 38, Folder 6)
    - Paula; 1995-02 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 38, Folder 7)
    - Paula; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 38, Folder 8)
    - Anne Gerber; 1995-05 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 38, Folder 9)
    - Anne Gerber Film Transfer Rolls 1,2; 1995-06-01 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min.; 00:22:00:00 (Carton 38, Folder 10)
    - Theme Evening, "Passages"; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 38, Folder 11)
    - [Ginsburg Memorial Footage and other footage]; undated (2 items), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 38, Folder 12)
    - Music of the 70s II & III; undated (2 items), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 38, Folder 13)
    - Bedroom Scene w: Chrissie Maryanne; 1992-03-28 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 38, Folder 14)
    - Pad [illegible] disk; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 38, Folder 15)